Time.
forever.
Sick at school, sick in the reading room, in front of the house, suddenly
When do you go suddenly?
It was a coincidence. To yourself
Do I need to know everything that happened?
So were you scared?
just. Do you want to wait?
I felt like I was pushing it too hard.
Did you hear well? No.
Don't lift it carefully.
Oh, don't be rude.
ah. like that
A miracle is not a railway, but our intelligence is a railway
I can't do it. Hey guys,
Dad came.
Are you here?
It looks like you're in a bad mood, so I'm not saying anything nonsense.
Just stay alert.
Try this too, Tteokgalbi? Kids
Okay, something like this?
First, I just went to meet a friend.
It's late. Coincidence.
You don’t think about anything else these days, right?
I work hard and do well at fruit.
Let's eat kimchi.
Oh, do you want to stop eating? Why stop again?
Eat? You have to eat well to get your head running well.
Mathematics is being neglected right around the corner.
Jeonghol. Come in and sit down
Raise your finger.
The voice actor will also be surprised. That's your problem.
Why do kids keep pooping?
Really? Ha.
I don't do anything and have no money. Really? Oh my.
When you scold children, you have to scold them harshly.
Is it okay to say something nice? I wonder if something happened at school
Did something happen? Professor Jeong said again
Did you fall? That’s what you’re curious about.
No, why suddenly? Also, I guess
I didn't do it, but I don't know you? every year
That's how you turn it around and ask, not like a human patient.
It's frustrating to see people like that every year.
Right? I have a social life like you said
That's it. It's so easy. That's easy.
What do people who stay at home know? The kids are straight
Look. Never mind.
I'm sorry, my dad is doing this because of my sister.
But I said it to you for no reason.
no. My mom ordered it
What? My brother is against my sister
Is everything controlled by mom behind the scenes? something real
He said, “You don’t like it?”
Mom doesn't like even a single word like that. Why don't you transfer?
You haven't met Green these days, have you? Still
I didn't solve it. Did you solve it?
What will Green solve before we meet?
What?
It's Acapul. yes.
Should I have said I would solve it?
You didn't believe it, did you?
So, do you just hate it or like it?
Whatever the reason, is it possible that it would be a good idea for the two of you to meet?
Isn’t what Greene trying to do is like breaking up a marriage?
I don't know if that's what my sister needs.
It's the capital, so hurry up and you'll be late.
Why are you going so fast? The atmosphere of the exam room is also
I can't climb like this.
Is that right? Huh
Smile, no, I'm going to the library.
Mom will give you a ride to the library.
No.
Look at me, brother, do you understand anything?
Who should go with you today during the day?
Dad goes home from work during the day after class is over. right away
Wow.
Cigar. back of the head
It tickles.
No, I was going to call you now. me first
Did you do it? no. I sang it first and lasted until the new year.
I was the first to call everyone.
Instruction manual: Song in one word
You shortened it. Then you can also say cell.
Yes, those childish pants are really forced.
It doesn't go well because it piles up.
germany. Why? Now tell me why only you guys
Do you know? You didn't tell me.
No, cancel?
I was going to say something. Because you're mom
I was so upset that I put it off. Sorry.
Oh, I really don't know anything. Hey
Don't cry, I already cried.
If I start again, I have to cry too, huh?
How did you get deathly ill? there
It's not like I'm going to live all the time, I'm going to go and not go
That's right, I might come back in a month.
If I marry a German man
It seems like there will be a lot of damage there.
Why do I live there?
Are you a descendant of Tangbun?
Are you trying to live with your mom? with your dad?
Are you going to live as long as you live?
After everything passes, we will become adults too, right?
You can make your own choices and take responsibility.
Yes, Terra, until then, please be a man
Be careful, man, be careful, love
Envoy: Are you as curious as I am now?
Just study, just study
Do it.
uh.
Hello professor, how are you?
Yes, he didn't come. What do you mean by that?
I am. It's definitely going in
I came to see it. What's going on?
Then, on your way, Odori
Didn't you see it? They said they didn’t go into the Odori testing center.
What?
I saw it.
It's a cod. Where does it come from
Huh? Where have you been so far?
Was there?
Nora, tell everything to your mom. you are the reason
I don't want to say it because I don't want to do it without it.
That complaint and that dog are you
You bullied me again so I hit you.
I can't do this, let's go to the hospital.
I'm afraid I'll lose my hair and not be able to study.
So you're afraid you'll be embarrassed? It's important to your mom.
That's the only thing, right?
Oh, why are you like that? Why are you like that?
You do that by putting everything into it and learning from it. what do i do
Being an older sister means confronting mom, lying, and other things.
He boasted about going to strange gatherings. The lie is from my mom
You know. what?
yes. What's going on? nothing
No. It's all about ballet. It's a lie. baby
Why do you say something to your sister when your mom gave it to you?
and. If I can't make rice cake soup, I'll throw it away.
Did my beggar mother tear it up? Do you know the picture well?
I'm going to throw it away too. like that
Where did the horse come from?
So what do you have a habit of saying to your mom? Ah honey, shout out
Do you come out? Come out.
I apologize to my mom quickly.
Originally, you didn't know what to say to me once.
They don’t even care about us and are always moms.
Just keep blaming and listen to Udo over there.
Dad, did you even see what those people were talking about? in society
Because I'm being ignored, I take out my anger on my family at home.
I said I was doing it. Dad is a coward.
But this guy, please calm down. father's corner
Come out.
Come and do it.
Ah, but these kids.
In the meantime, I Just me
Other than that, my family would be perfect.
I thought about it. This is
It was perfect, but it was a mistake.
Everyone was wearing masks.
It seemed perfect. Even my brother.
uh.
I'll come back.
what? Are you here yet?
Aren't you there? Director.
Wow, that's crazy.
Don't you remember?
What kind of outfit were we wearing when we first met?
They call it the way Lynn liked it the most.
Didn't I tell you? Where's the director?
Are you there? The director’s car was stuck, so
You're late. It’s been a while since we waited for you to eat
Shall we talk about the past? old story
Have fun alone.
Why did I come willingly, knowing I was a marquis?
Let's go back to the old days. we.
I did everything wrong, please forgive me.
It's okay, that could happen.
Instead? I forgive you too
Will you give me what?
C.
It's still the same to interrupt others without A.
I'll tell you next, even though I know it's a trick, I'm willing
The reason I came was to reassure my man.
I didn't meet goodness because I was lonely.
Even when I was dating you, my preference was always ahead of you.
Back then and even now, I was so scared that I couldn’t overcome it.
Now, others.
okay.
What are you doing here? Are you on emergency standby?
Press it.
That's right, what should I do?
Did you miss me?
Well, me too.
Fincon did as he said. To reassure my man
He confidently said he was out.
I was really ugly.
Why did I do that? Are you embarrassed?
I'll just keep it to myself. But really, why did you do that?
First of all, not like an answer.
It's the rain of a patient with unrequited love.
I gained a lot of weight.
I liked it for a long time. what?
Hey, why didn't you come yesterday?
We shouldn't fool around, Oz.
I'm sorry, Dad. Oh, I apologize.
what?
My dad passed away last year.
you.
It's okay again, I'm okay
It's okay. But why are you
Are you crying? What happened yesterday?
Why is it increasing like this?
Even if you don't show it, it won't increase any more
It must have been difficult. Ah.
yes.
ah.
I told you not to cry.
I think it was probably from then on.
i am you like it
What happened?
Why why didn't you tell me? why
Wouldn't you have done it? Is it a car?
You saw it, you know what.
I'm old.
eww.
Brother.
Did you want to take a picture?
uh. Go to Africa.
I also want to take pictures of zebras and lions.
I want to go to the desert and take pictures of stars.
what's this?
It's National Geographic. There's a picture there
Huh. Was that a dream?
I think you are the best in our house
I thought I would get freedom first.
Because I'm the worst.
There are no ugly people? I just have to be myself.
That's it. What do you want to do?
Instead, be tactful.
Why doesn’t my male friend date a good boyfriend?
Did you fight? It came out
I don't know what it is, but it's been too long
Don't drag it. Then really
Does that happen? I
Are you going to go to the lab? Go in first.
Brother.
I'm sure it will come next week.
huh.
Laugh.
sun.
It came, it came, it came, is it inside?
phew.
mom.
Um, why are you looking at the sidewalk?
There is a kitchen, right? There is no one in the house.
Is it nowhere to be found?
It's so noisy it's killing me.
yes.
I'm in big trouble. I guess there's a body at home.
What did you say you left your dream house?
Dong-gu.
hello?
why? that is?
Do I have something to say to my brother-in-law?
I'm going to make it so I'm hanging up. You don’t have to go in, just wait.
Listen to me. uh.
The winning village. by chance
When I leave my brother-in-law's house, I also meet a coincidence.
Why do you think we should break up?
Every mouse is good, right? Oh, that's not true.
Call me, let's meet for a moment and give advice.
Can you do something and leave?
Brother-in-law, can you say something before you leave?
Okay? Send it first.
So, yes, please come.
Don't tell anyone. Of course that
I'll be busy for 1,000 won, so 10 minutes
Let’s meet for ten minutes.
Oh yeah?
I don't think we said anything, but that's it.
Fortunately, it wasn't too far away. Know.
Does that mean it works?
Your magnetism is off.
To voicemail. Herzos
Location tracking is bulging.
Did you find it? I didn’t find it.
Ha, not yet
Are you here?
yes.
Yes ah You said it earlier.
Are you going to visit the complex next door?
Why is this happening twice a day?
Who is Uidori’s first best friend?
uh.
I don't know the number. Have you seen something like this?
uh. hmm.
Did it break? Uh.
Come here.
Your phone is off, so it goes to voicemail.
Connection.
Has it grown?
under.
Where is Bonggu’s house?
Udeul, why are you
Did you run away from the exam room?
I don't like it, so I test it too
You don’t like it?
It's Dong-gu. Did you come to say goodbye?
Am I going to leave the house? If I go to Silla
Who will raise me?
Can I raise you? Because I'm smart, I can grow up alone
Are you confident? Are you confident?
Is it okay if it’s not just the Chumuriz?
I don't want to see it anymore.
Do you want to go with me too?
No. Grandma will be sad
Are you sure?
I just tried it.
Why do I have to go to Hanwha so quickly? Who is it?
Pervert Goi. my sister
They say they have a problem to discuss.
Ah, it's fun. to.
Good, right?
uh.
step. Don't tell anyone.
Mistress little guest.
Uh huh?
It's okay, call me.
Is this a promotion?
Are you okay? Just a light bruise?
I was so surprised that I fainted for a moment, and the plaintiff's grandmother also
Did you say it was okay?
Because of heavy rain. Because of you
No dude um?
let's go. I will wait for the manuscript.
hand.
Why are you really a child?
Laugh.
under.
sorry. Because of my child.
sorry. are you okay. When the kids play
It could be so.
Rather. Below is the
Are you so surprised? Your face
As it is known. It was good.
Aren’t you scolding me? 0.002
Play with me, voice actor idol.
Gudora. Laugh.
Was my gentle mother at fault?
I won't do that again.
That's right, come to us.
mom.
uh.
eww.
By the way. the student
Where did you go? The key that saved you
Big student, that's right, where are you really?
You went, right? Oh, I couldn't even say thank you.
grandma big student
No, it's Woodoli's boat.
Huh?Mom, that’s really it
If I wasn't a student, I would have been in big trouble.
They said it was just a passing road, but it was really too much.
Thank you, I should say hello, so just
Did you go?
Eun, where are you going? Ah,
Why?Why?
uh. uh.
mom. dad. passing by
Not a student?
boy friend. uh.
What? Of the stipulated personnel.
My mom and dad.
Ah, hello. My name is Namjeong.
What are you talking about now?
Hee-seong. you.
Didn't you see it?
Soyeon. The beast.
hi.
I did something.
ah. again
A dream.
Everything is gone again.
right.
ha.
What's going on at this time?
We're rebelling right now.
divagation. finish
Welcome. Then go
Can you look at me for a moment?
4 characters for about 30 minutes
Hello to Rijab Leaf.
Binding.
This is where I really want to come. again
Because I thought you wouldn’t come. from now on.
Yes, 2 units.
Sorry. me too.
What are you feeling?
I did it all badly. Didn’t you just feel bad?
It's all because I'm petty.
Because you like it.
I think I'm a really good person
As a result, I became more and more greedy.
I think so.
Sorry.
Because it was hard.
Are you a good person?
Can I become more greedy? I
While living. Who has never made it big
Do you ever care or anything?
So, how embarrassed were you at first?
I'm worried again and again
Good. I feel anxious again.
anyway. you to me
It's my first time with anything.
To me again and again
It hurts half, right?
Lee Jeong-ah.
afoot.
Is that right Jisung?
me.
Do I have a crush on you?
weird. Why do you work so hard? To people today
Have you ever lost your temper? Agency proposal
I must have received it. Is this not an amateur anymore?
I really feel like a celebrity
It seems like it might be.
I feel a little strange.
Because the child I always play with is eager.
I also want to do something.
Don't you?
I'll never be alone like that
Do you want to do it?
uh.
Are you here?
I heard you're going to Germany?
It's ambiguous.
It's too much of a pastoral relationship to say goodbye seriously.
I think I'll regret it forever if I pretend I didn't see it.
omg. hmm.
Do you think you'll be kicking the blanket forever?
At least do it directly.
If you make a noise now, it will kick you in the mouth for a long time.
You should do it, right?
Am I just going to remain a boring guy like this?
Ah, I hesitated, never knowing that I would end up like this.
Okay?
That's not it.
come back again
I'm going to start from then.
What, you don't want to come in. uh.
Did you do well? Have a nice trip.
I liked it for a long time. I'm old.
what's the matter? This time?
Do you have anything to say?
Is it me first?
uh. in fact?
Actually, today I am a new man
When he came in, he said he was handsome.
Hey, hey, middle school is good-looking, so that’s it.
Talk and draw pictures.
why? But medical school?
one.
So I couldn't say it. how
I tell you that my heart fluttered as soon as I saw you for the first time.
Isn't that right? Isn't it supposed to be a grid in perception and attitude?
Feel refreshed now.
In Antarctica. Get on a plane.
really?
Ha, customer. Going
We will take you safely to the road.
Today, I thought, just forget about it from tomorrow.
Just give it a try.
uh.
Oh, I was fooled, Mom, I'm waiting for you right now.
Where are you?
Professor, where does he go to school?
It's not him, it's me
Now that I know, where is the school?
Put away the cold stuff, you're crazy.
Why? Why is it cold?
What are your parents doing?
good night. He's fine. It looks like he's cold.
There is. my family
What's so great about us?
The house is such a mess, what is this?
okay. Ah, you deserve to be a mother.
No, I said something off topic. I'm like that
It's not a story. Why did you suddenly catch my mother’s weakness?
In times like this, you should use it.
I'd like to if I could, but
No, I don't. Why did mom do that?
My first concern was what the story was.
It's unfair to me too, I hate my mom and hate her a lot.
I want to, but it doesn't work.
Mom, you punish me and treat me harshly, but you don’t
It's so unfair that I hate you.
however.
Is it a word for good luck? One element
Would you have done that, Mom?
What works well? all
It's my mother's standard. What is the standard? How much is it?
Let’s hear how great it is.
While drawing my favorite picture.
Sequel to living happily ever after
shout out
Say what you like and explain it all. I'll be happy
I wasn't happy because I didn't want to know.
He told me to quit, so I listened.
I want to keep misunderstanding the structure
You don’t like it either, right?
To ballet.
It must be quite fun because you have some talent, right?
When kids envy me, I feel flattered.
One day. I have money to buy ballet shoes
Did a poor kid come to our academy?
I just happened to buy new shoes and wear the shoes I used to wear.
Did you give it to your friend?
Can I have it here?
Well I bought it myself
Thank you so much. But you
You can't continue ballet? This is a lot of money
Listen, my mom always nags me.
I know, I know too. never
I won't give up, I think like that
Seunghee was fun. Until then?
Now, the next demonstration is you.
He is calling.
Park Seung-hee, let’s do it.
Me? I was born
It was the day I first tasted humiliation.
Living happily while doing what you like.
Does this only apply to kids who are good at something?
That's why I quit, I couldn't quit, Grandpa
Because my grandmother was against being a teacher.
Thanks to you, I was that friend before I joined the ballet company.
Are you just following me around?
So it didn't go in even if you applied it? That's right.
Maybe he quit because he got hurt? No.
Getting hurt was a win, huh?
There was a power outage in the middle of rehearsal and there was an accident.
Did you wake up? It turned out that I was the culprit.
At just the right time, my father's business went bankrupt.
So, I just quit that path without any regrets.
Why did you let people misunderstand? It's not unfair, hey
It's just worse than what I'm getting now.
Better.
Does it make you happy to hear crappy stories? hmm.
It's a great lie that no one will believe anyway
A hundred times more.
Do I trust you, Mom? And the crummy one is
Much better. why
Are you talking about that day? And ever again
You didn’t hear, I said it was difficult. Like you
I can't stand the cycle, I don't know anything anymore
If your mom and dad are against it, just don't go to college.
I'm going to go and draw, and I'm going to get a part-time job and become independent.
I will continue to date even the captain.
Look. Now I tell my mom regularly
You're really good at talking back, haha.
Let’s not talk. I? No, but
Who is stubborn about being wrong?
That's because you resemble your mother, so don't be like your mother.
Don't you like it? I'm a mom
She is a daughter, looks like her mother, and lives like her mother.
Yes.
therefore. From now on
Just disappear nicely. huh.
Then we.
So this isn't going to come?
Uh uh, accidental.
why?
Do you want to go out like that after eating?
Singular?
When Heejeong destroys this?
We also hid our glorious childhood.
It is very difficult to iron a child's diaper. Really
Oh, don't grow up.
Think of it roughly like this. The diaper
The older you get, the thicker your wallet becomes. pretty
We heard that he will introduce you to his girlfriend too.
Woman, girlfriend.
So, throw this away now.
Let’s get ready for the new era.
Three eras.
Ah Jeong-ah, Mipe instead.
Here.
Park Kyung.
Read this. Ah, this is it.
These are the people who will fix this. I travel across the country
Did you search and find it?
Hey, this is a mess, but wouldn't it be easy? me too
Uh, I mean. Eat and give me ah
What to eat, what to eat, we can't fix it
All I have is my personality. Yes Brother.
It doesn't work?
I remember our childhood
It was obvious, don’t worry, I would never
It won't change. never never
Absolutely you.
Guess what.
New era.
barely we
Returned to daily life.
Is this an afterthought?
When I returned. Somehow, he’s younger than me
It was the same. no. So
Was I better than the dead?
The dead left again
Huh?
I'm so sorry for the things I said to my young mother.
It didn't try to fall. in the end
195 countries around the world
It became a response pants for memorizing the capitals.
My mom gave permission for a spy meeting.
That wasn't all. Hanolge music
Wait a minute.
Today is the day to register for academy fees, right?
over three months
Register and change the canvas
Change your clothes too.
Thank you. With that kind of drawing skill, what kind of Seoul National University can you get?
He asked if I could go.
Sent to art academy.
There's a fact.
Is this a paperback book? Ah,
Then why should I throw it away?
Eat? Are you looking for this?
Oh, so what?
Demolition.
Hyeran goes to Germany with her mother.
I left.
Sun Seon’s enlistment date is quickly approaching.
Ki Jeong-in, in his own words, is a promising person.
He said it was a planned gemstone and unlike before, he was busy with work.
I became more serious.
today. On the sting
It's the last day to go out.
While preparing for high school seniors, I am a mother until this day.
As I said, I decided to go all in on the entrance exam.
What about your sisters and brothers?
In this place, without change.
He said he would wait.
ah.
Domestic joint payment.
Oh no matter what the sports concept is
Even if you play ball indoors
It's prohibited. Dadada dada
Look here. Our Red.
I casted it this time. It's good news.
What's wrong? Every time I audition
I told him to smoke, so I clenched my teeth and acted.
I practiced. What is your role?
Convenience store part-timer, here's the line, witchcraft or something.
There is. Oh there are two lines
Medium size. fall down
Wow. handsome
It would be an issue if I were to play a part-time job at a convenience store.
Hey, do you want to get my autograph? 1st
Do it first and then tell me. I am
Why are you giving me a reporter? ah.
Oh, did you do your hair like that?
Ah, blind date because of the blind date.
Yes, for some reason I have to do it too. romantic relationship.
The main character is late today. Oh, it's time for that.
They say there is. Coming with your head shaved
No, Paul.
No, are you saying I’m leaving now?
But where?
I didn't cut it?
what? Why are you crying all of a sudden?
My sister is not in your head
Do you feel lost just because you came?
Ah. really?
hmm. why
Don't cry, okay?
This time I will wait for you, me and us
It's a woman.
Oh, what are you doing? What should I do if someone sees it?
Ah? I want to see Nam’s picture.
What should I do?
Oh what what what what what?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No.
also. Ah
Wang Soteo. again
So what happens?
15th.
The ball came to me. Don't get closer.
Hasn’t red changed a lot too? Well, that's right.
I'm talking about it now, but it was actually my first time seeing it.
I was really scared at that time.
I was more scared when I was in middle school, even now
It's scary. Let’s take a closer look with Woohyun.
Stand up straight. report
There is. I'm going to go to the middle of the day.
Ah, but that kind of uncle is also the best
It hasn't changed much. What did I say
Uh, at first, I always wore the same clothes
You wore it. The uniform I couldn't wear
It's true, look at it now. In the concept
This is my first sincerity. Now that I think about it, I see.
Well, if we didn't meet each other much then
I'm still drunk in the corner of my room
There must have been. Honestly, at this age
It's not easy to hang out somewhere.
Thank you everyone for playing with me
If she is the first king, she will die in front of the chrysalis.
I have had enemies too. picture
I like it, but what does age have to do with it?
Is that right?
It's cool to say things like that.
so beautiful
Yes.
wait a minute. uh.
mom. Hanok and
Do you think I'll go home after dinner because of my gender?
okay? I'll come in without being late.
hmm.
uh.
Sorry, but wait
Do you have time?
Me?
Sometimes I think about that.
If you didn't meet the specifications that day
What happened? My friends
If you came a little early, buy a model.
What if you refused?
If so? Here and now
No one, right?
Me and my dreams too.
babe.
Born a long time ago. fantasy
Only things that are likely to happen inside
I used to imagine it.
Is it worth dreaming in reality?
Because I was too scared.
but. for now
Don't look.
I, too, can do something like this.
If I change, my world too
That it changes.
I'm still timid.
I am anxious about what will happen in the future.
Still, I won't give up ahead of time.
because.
Jo Hyeon-ah, what are you doing here?
Because I.
The only one in the world.
We have a special distribution team.
uh. now
Click right away.
I'm having a boyfriend
Like an idea.
yes. now.
excuse me.
me.
Briefing course.
Hello love.